

ABOUT ME

I'm an impact-driven product designer with over five years of multinational experience in various industries. My passion lies in crafting meaningful and impactful digital products. I also strive to help brands improve their digital experiences that address user needs and business goals.

TECH SKILLS

DESIGN DEVELOPMENT TOOLS TOOLS

Figma HTML/CSS
Sketch Javascript/jQuery
Adobe CC Google Analytics
Principle Git/GitHub
Overflow Zeplin
Miro Hotjar

COMPETENCIES

Visual Design
Experience Design
Interaction Design
Interface Design
Design System

Wireframing Prototyping Info Architecture User Interview Usability Testing

EDUCATION

SIMON FRASER UNIVERSITY

B/A - Interactive Arts + Technology Design Concentration

Graduated with Distinction and Co-op Education Award 2014 - 2019

ACHIEVEMENTS

DEAN'S HONOR ROLL

FALL 2014

Awarded to students for achieving a 3.50 (out of 4.33) or higher GPA.

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

Product Designer / Shopee

JUL 2022 - PRESENT

- Improving the seller centre and buyer marketplace experience based on the existing regional design guidelines.
- Communicating with cross functional teams to develop solutions, receive feedback, and manage multiple projects in a fast-paced environment.

Senior Product Designer / Tokoplas

SEP 2020 - JUN 2022

- Working together with management and engineers to redefine the user experience of the e-commerce website, seller portal, and mobile apps.
- Leading the design efforts of the new website and seller portal as well as creating design system, mockups, and prototypes for development.

UX/UI Designer / Zaui Software

DEC 2019 - APR 2020

- Collaborated with engineers and product experts to design flows and features for the new web booking engine and back-office platform.
- Developed wireframes, high-fidelity mockups, and interactive prototypes for the new web booking engine and back-office platform.

Digital Designer / PayByPhone

OCT 2018 - APR 2019

- Redefined the user experience and designed the interface of the new parking operators (B2B) and careers pages.
- Produced marketing materials for print and digital such as promotional banners, posters, postcards, display ads, and social media graphics.

UX/UI Designer / BSTRO

MAY - SEP 2018

- Collaborated with senior designers in designing digital experiences for Johnson & Johnson, Chef Software, and The San Francisco Marathon.
- Day-to-day included creative concepting, competitive analysis, sitemap drafting, wireframing, mockups design, and prototyping.

UX/UI Designer / BuzzIt Inc.

SEP 2017 - AUG 2018

- Worked collaboratively with a product manager and a developer in redesigning Buzzlt's website and mobile apps in a startup environment.
- Overhauled the visual design and user experience of the entire Android & iOS app by producing 50+ sets of end to end mockups.